

- +6011-36973155
- wsuan15@gmail.com

 B-328 Blok B Lorong CP 2/10
- Cheras Perdana Apartment
 43200 Batu 9 Cheras Selangor

https://github.com/frank1176

https://www.linkedin.com/in/frankie-lim-aa7895233/

Internship Period:

20th November 2023 - 5th May 2024

SKILL

- HTML, CSS
- JavaScript
- Leaflet
- Python
- Java
- C
- PHP
- Git
- Django
- WordPress
- PostgreSQL

LANGUAGE

- Mandarin
- English
- Malay

PROJECT

- Auto Vehicle Location System(AVLS)
- Automated waste sorting system by Robotic Arms

LIM WAI MIN

Internship

ABOUT ME

Interested and Passionate in the IT industry. I have experience in developing with Django RESTful API and Angular Framework. Passionate about IoT and computer vision. In my free time, I will enjoy jogging for relaxation. I am willing to embrace new challenges and continuous learning to enhance my skills within the IT industry.

WORK EXPERIENCE

O Jan 2021- Present TigaKY.SDN.BHD, Petaling Jaya, Malaysia Internship Software Engineer

mostly work on the backend side such as maintaining backend database servers, manipulating data, and creating a functional CRUD combined with front-end codes.

• Achievements: Participating in the Auto Vehicle Location System (AVLS) project from start to end.

CO-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

) Jan 2021- Present

Medical Awareness Camp Outreach(MACO), Petaling Jaya, Malaysia

Volunteer

Help refurbished Computers and Laptops for Medical Awareness

Camp Outreach to donate.

EDUCATION

Q 2019 - 2021

New Era University College (NEUC)

Diploma in Web Development

CGPA:3.50

o 2021 - Present

Tunku Abdul Rahman University of Management and Technology (TARUMT) Bachelor of Software Engineer

CGPA:3.2777

REFERENCES

Kenny Khoo

Director, TigaKY.SDN.BHD

Phone: +6012-2259712 Email: k@3ky.my